[{"id": 2611, "question": "Matt grow the best vegetables in the village.He grows fruit too--big , sweet apples and oranges.And what else ? Well , the biggest and the prettiest flowers.Things grow in Matt' s garden all through the year.He cuts some flowers for his sitting room table ; and of course , he eats some fruit and vegetables.But he sells everything else in the market.Matt is not a poor man. He knows a few other gardens ; but he does not have any friends.You might ask , \" What is that ? Why doesn ' t he have friends ? \" I will tell you.People do not understand him.And they do not understand his garden, \" Why not ? \" you will ask.\" It' s a very good garden , isn' t it ? \" It is a wonderful garden.Matt plants things in spring , summer and autumn and winter .After that he does very little work.He sits in the gar...\n\nQ: Matt makes a living by    _   .", "options": ["selling his vegetables , fruit and flowers", "growing trees in his garden", "working in the market", "helping other people growing plants"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 461, "question": "High school announcements Do you have a high school announcement to make? Are you hosting a high school sports event or tournament? Are you looking for a coach? Let us know, and we'll share it with \"Tribune\" readers. August 21---- Sacred Heart is looking for two assistant baseball coaches immediately. Practices and games are held after school at 3:30 pm. Some experience in playing or coaching is preferred. If interested, e-mail Ron Schwartz at ramsad1@aol.com. August 7 ----- Loyola Academy will host its 12th Rambler Baseball Winter Workshop for students in fourth through eighth grades on Aug. 26. the early registration fee is $70 and registration at the door is $85. contact Loyola coach Bill San Hamel at 847-920-2523 to register early. July 17 ----- St. Patrick will host a Youth Holiday Ba...\n\nQ: If one wants to choose a relatively cheap sports camp, he may   _  .", "options": ["phone 847-920-2523 to register early", "e-mail connolly.marypat@marist.net", "visit www.athletics2000.com/bartlett", "contact head wrestling coach Jason Hayes"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 952, "question": "Three years ago when I was still in the University, I also worked at a restaurant. An old man named Mr. Candido Filio was one of our regular customer at the restaurant. He was one of the most intelligent people I've ever known. Every Sunday the Philippine Star Newspaper had a special page for word puzzles and among his peers , Mr.Filio held the record for solving all the puzzles in less than five minutes. He encouraged me to solve them too, and for months and months, I did my best to beat him but failed. Then one Sunday, I did it! I was able to complete them before anyone else. Everyone cheered for me. He came up to me with a smile and said, \" No one has ever beaten me before. You are the first. I'll have a prize for you tomorrow.\" The next day, he gave me a special Scrabble set. I would h...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that Mr.Filio  _", "options": ["was generous to young people", "was good at word puzzles", "lived quite near the restaurant", "won a prize from the Philippine Star Newspaper"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1983, "question": "Why are so many students not doing well? Why is there such a huge achievement gap between urban and suburban students? Just this week, in my school the seventh grade team leader called a meeting to discuss academic detention . The purpose of the detention is to allow students who are doing poorly a second chance to redo the work. Now if a student did not understand an assignment I have no trouble allowing that student to redo a test or give some extra credit work, but if a student did poorly because he/she opted not to do the work out of sheer laziness, that student should not be given a second chance. And parents should be held accountable for their children. That is another reason why there is such a huge achievement gap. All children should be monitored at home in order to achieve great...\n\nQ: The seventh grade team leader in the author's school called    a meeting to   _  .", "options": ["analyse the reason for the huge achievement gap between students", "find out who is to blame for the huge achievement gap between students", "talk about giving students who are doing poorly a second chance to redo the work", "discuss how to narrow the huge achievement gap between students"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 191, "question": "Boys' schools are the perfect place to teach young men to express their emotions and involve them in activities such as art, dance and music. Far from the traditional image of a culture of aggressive masculinity ,the absence of girls gives boys the chance to develop without pressure to be consistent to a stereotype ,a US study says. Boys at single-sex schools were said to be more likely to get involved in cultural and artistic activities that helped develop their abilities to express their emotions,rather than feeling they had to obey to the\"boy code\"of hiding their emotions to be a\"real man\". The findings of the study are against the received wisdom that boys do better when taught alongside girls. Tony Little,headmaster of Eton,warned that boys were being ignored by the British education ...\n\nQ: According to Abigail James,one of the advantages of single-sex schools is  _  .", "options": ["teaching can be adapted to suit the characteristics of boys", "boys can focus on their lessons without being absent-minded", "boys can choose to learn whatever they are interested in", "teaching can be designed to promote boys'team spirit"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1966, "question": "Here is some general information about Edison Elementary School. For more information, you can visit our website which is printed on the cover. Attendance: Please contact the office at 480. 472. 5282 if your child is going to be absent. Renaissance Reading: The Accelerated Reader (AR) Program is a computerized reading enrichment program that combines great children's literature with computer skills. As an individualized reading program, it is designed to motivate students to read more and to read good literature. Students of different abilities can use this program. It is not a competitive program but one that improves any student's reading ability. Here is how it works. Students select books in their reading range from our Accelerated Reader Selection and read it at their own pace. Once t...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about how Renaissance Reading works?", "options": ["Students select books based on the instruction of the computer.", "Students take the quiz without others' arrangements.", "The result of the quiz will be kept by teachers.", "The summary of the book to be selected is shown on the screen."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1265, "question": "I live in north Celebes which is near Philippines. Since early December 2010 most tropical regions have been frequently hit by rain. Just like my hometown, tropical regions only have two seasons, including the dry season that usually starts from April to September and the wet or rainy season which usually happens from October to March. But, it could be _ Sometimes the rainy season can come a month earlier or later. It can be prolonged even more than 4 months and so can the dry season. Even during the dry season, rain can occur several times in certain areas. The prolonged dry season in tropical areas usually causes a lot of losses. It will be very harmful to local farmers, because most of the tropical areas sre regions of the developing countries. Sometimes agricultural and plantation crop...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that in the wet season,   _", "options": ["the capital of Jakarta is flooded every year", "more crops will die after being flooded for so long.", "mosquitoes will spread more diseases among the crowd.", "people with weak immune might be attacked by some diseases"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 914, "question": "HOGN KONG--Nine out of 10 Singapore citizens returned dropped wallets with money in them,but in Hone Kong only three out of l0 wallets were returned in an honesty test carried out in Asian cities by Readers Digest . Larger cities did worse while in general people in smaller places returned secretly planted wallets,results from the experiment showed. Readers Digest secretly scattered 140 wallets all over Asia,each with a name,address and phone number,family pictures,notes and money in it. The magazine workers then watched to see what happened.South Koreans in Seoul returned six out of the ten dropped wallets,while those in Inchon returned eight. 50 percent of Be dropped wallets were returned in Bombay,Bangkok,Taipei and Kajang in Malaysia,with most people saying they would not keep what was...\n\nQ: Which people as a group did best in the honesty tests?", "options": ["People in Hong Kong.", "People in the United States.", "People in Inchon.", "People in Singapore."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2996, "question": "With my hands and knees on the floor of the airplane, I was searching for an old lady's missing hearing aid during the flight from Sydney to Los Angeles. It occurred to me that this may not be the most dignified posture for a Buddhist nun . I had seen the old lady from the seat in front of me as she walked up and down the passage with a flashlight. I asked a few times what was wrong, but she didn't answer at first --- she couldn't hear me. She was wearing a woolen coat. Judging from her accent, she came from Eastern Europe. Do you know what hearing aids cost? Thousands, especially for the new tiny hidden-in-the-ear type she described. It takes a long time for an appointment to make a new one, and many doctor visits to get the thing adjusted right. Therefore, my dignity seemed less importan...\n\nQ: Why did the author put her hands and knees on the floor?", "options": ["She is a religious Buddhist nun.", "She fell down from her seat.", "She helped the old lady look for her hearing aid.", "She wanted to stand out among the passengers."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 899, "question": "It is true that the first Olympic Games of the modern times in 1896 were not open to women.Baron Pierre de Coubertin,who gave new life to the Games,was very much a man of his time.He didn't like women showing up for the Games.But since this time,things have changed.History shows that the number of women participating in the Olympic Games has been increasing over the years,since their first participation in the 1900 Olympic Games and especially in the last 30 years.This development is of social,political and cultural significance . The progress is the result of the cooperation of the entire Olympic Movement and of proper measures that the International Olympic Committee(IOC),International Sports Federations(IFs),and National Olympic Committees(NOCs)have taken.Especially in the last 20 years...\n\nQ: It is implied in the passage that    .", "options": ["women first performed in the Olympic Games about fifty years ago", "it was IFs that decided to enlarge the women's programme at the Olympic Games", "Juan Antonio Samaranch didn't agree that women should be IOC members", "women themselves worked very hard so that they could join in the Olympic Games"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2951, "question": "The Streisand Effect When Barbra Streisand discovered in 2003 that a photograph of her California beach house was among 12,000 photos on the Internet as part of a collection by a photographer Kenneth Adelman, she did what any famous person would do: hit him with a $50 million lawsuit . But in trying to hold back the images, she caused a different result. Her legal actions led to almost half a million people visiting the website, viewing and copying the photos within a month. Ever since then, the effect of letting public know something you are trying to keep secret has been called the \"Streisand effect\". The problem for anyone trying to cover up information is that the Internet is the world's biggest and most useful copying machine. Put a document on to a connected machine and it will sprea...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from the passage?", "options": ["Streisand effect does good to most famous people.", "It's not a good idea to argue against authorities.", "The ban on something may have opposite effect.", "Turning to the law is a perfect way to get one out of trouble."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3334, "question": "Japan Earthquake and Tsunami :How to Help For readers interested in contributing to help victims of the earthquake and tsunami that struck Japan and the Pacific region,here is a list of contact information and links for some agencies that plan to provide relief. THE JAPAN CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL EXCHANGE The Japan Center for International Exchange has set up the Japan NGO Earthquake Relief and Recovery Fund.Half of the money raised will go to support six Japanese NGOs currently at work in the disaster area and half will be retained to support the longer term recovery. AMERICAN RED CROSS Red Cross officials say donors can text REDCROSS to 90999 and a $10 donation will automatically be charged to donors' phone bill,or donations can be made directly on its Web site. B'NAI B'RITH INTERNATIONA...\n\nQ: What do we know about CARE from the text?", "options": ["It opened a Person Finder Page online.", "It is the world's largest humanitarian organization.", "It raised much money to support six Japanese NGOs.", "It warned its staff in Asia of the danger of tsunami."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1942, "question": "My description of a hero is a person who _ his all for others. A person who puts others before himself.A person who does ordinary things, not because they have to, but because they want to. So I got to think who are my heroes? Several people came to mind. But there was one that really stuck out in my mind. I guess I really thought about it, but this man really is my hero. This man is my dad. I know,we all think our dads are our heroes. But the truth is, I really can't ever remenber thinking of my dad really as a hero. I am sure that I have said that he was. But I an not sure if I ever really thought about in terms of what is a hero?I mean he never saved anyone's life. He never fought in a war. He never invented anything to make life easier for others. But as I thought of his qualities. I f...\n\nQ: The writer  believes his father is a hero because   _  .", "options": ["his father saved people's lives", "he fought in a war bravely", "he invented something to make life easier for others", "he does ordinary things that he wants to do for families."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2443, "question": "It's not easy to find a person with the qualities it takes to be a hero. I didn't really understand the meaning of the word \"hero\" until my third year in the college. If you saw her, you wouldn't think she really looks the part, but she is stronger than Superman could ever be. Her name is Sandra Keierleber. I first met her at volleyball tryouts , but didn't notice anything special at first. As the week passed, however, she showed she had more heart than anyone. She stood out because she never gave up, no matter what. Sandra isn't the tallest or the fastest --- in fact, this was her first time playing volleyball and it showed--- but that didn't stop her. She was always the first to arrive and the last to leave. By the end of tryouts she had found a place in everyone's heart. When the name l...\n\nQ: What did the writer think of Sandra Keierleber at the beginning?", "options": ["Common", "Honest", "Pretty.", "Strong"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1322, "question": "Growing up in one of the poorest, most crime-ridden communities on the south side of Atlanta, US, being raised by a single mother who didn't finish 3rd grade, living each day on food stamps and attending what the media called \"the most dysfunctional public school district,\" not many people expected much of me, so I had to expect something of myself. On my 13th birthday, I bought a poster of Harvard to hang in my room. Being at Harvard became what I dreamt about: I saw myself attending class in Sanders Theater, studying in Widener Library and eating in Annenberg Hall. Even when my electricity was cut off and I woke up at 5:30 a.m. to pitch blackness, I knew that my poster of Harvard was still hanging only two feet away from me. I'd begin my day by asking myself these two questions, \"What do...\n\nQ: What's the author's attitude towards \"poverty\"?", "options": ["Disappointed.", "Objective.", "Thankful.", "Sad."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3353, "question": "Willie Stewart still remembers his first day of kayaking through the grand Canyon. He was getting bounced around in the roughest white water he had ever seen. There was nothing the river threw at him. There he was in a 40-pound boat, with only a few months of training and one arm. Tied to his left shoulder was a prosthetic limb that he'd had for just about a week. The plan was to paddle for 20 days over 227 miles of the roughest white water in the United States. It was one of the most remarkable adventures that the Grand Canyon had ever seen. It started with a casual phone call in the spring of 2005. A good friend, Mike Crenshaw, finally got a permit from the National Park Service to lead a private party of 16 boaters down the Colorado River that coming August. He had a slot open for Willi...\n\nQ: What can we learn form the story ?", "options": ["An optimist sees the rose ; a pessimist sees the thorn", "Nothing is too difficult if you put your heart into it", "A change of self is needed more than a change of scene", "If winter comes, can spring be far away ?"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3234, "question": "This Monday,the nation will start to celebrate Presidents' Day,just seven days before George Washington's birthday.Everyone agrees that day is a holiday,but is it just to celebrate George Washington's Birthday? What about Abraham Lincoln? Some government offices call it Presidents' Day.Others say the holiday is officially Washington's Birthday.Confused yet? George Washington was elected the country's first President on April 30,1789.Soon after,Americans began publicly celebrating his birthday.Presidential historians say the actual date of George Washington's birth is February 11,1732.But a change in the calendar system 20 years later shifted all dates,making Washington's birthday February 22,which is now well accepted.In 1879.Congress made Washington's birthday an official federal holiday....\n\nQ: What's the main argument about this holiday?", "options": ["When to celebrate the holiday.", "How to celebrate the holiday.", "Which president to honor.", "Where to celebrate the holiday."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 362, "question": "Now that America has declared a state of swine flu public health emergency, you may be asking yourself -- what am Isupposed to do? Here is a list of practical steps you can take to prepare and protect yourself and your family. 1) Know the symptoms-- Here are some of the symptoms that sound like swine flu -- fevers over 100 degrees (37.8degC), body aches, cough, runny nose, and sometimes, nausea and diarrhea . It's also useful to know if you might have had an exposure either by recent travel to Mexico, or to the areas of known cases so far in America -- specific areas of California, Texas, New York, Ohio and Kansas. Or you may have been exposed to a sick person who came from those areas. 2) Don't panic-- If you have symptoms that sound like swine flu, do not rush to hospitals. Not only is t...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT a suggestion given by the writer?", "options": ["Cough and sneeze into your hands.", "Wash your hands and wear a mask.", "Go on eating pork if you like.", "Store some food and medicine at home."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2508, "question": "No one knows for certain why people dream, but some dreams misht be connected to the mental processes that help us learn. In a recent study, scientists found a connection between nap-time dreams and better memory in people who were learning a new skill. \"I was astonished by this finding,\" Robert Stickgold told Science News. He is a cognitive neuroscientist at Harvard Medical School who worked on the study of-how the brain and nervous system work, and cognitive studies look at how people learn and reason. So a cognitive neuroscientist may study the brain processes that help people learn. In the study, 99 college students between the ages of 18 and 30 each spent an hour on a computer, trying to get through a virtual maze . The maze was difficult, and the study participants had to start in a ...\n\nQ: The better performance in working out the maze is connected with  _  .", "options": ["how people dream", "what people dream", "when people dream", "where people dream"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1597, "question": "One day about 30 years ago, a 2 year-old Chinese boy in Shenyang was watching a Tom and Jerry cartoon on TV. Tom the cat began to play the piano. The music was to beautiful that the boy fell in love with it at once. This little boy was Lang Lang - one of today's great pianists. Lang Lang began to play the piano at 3. By the age of 5, the had won fist place in Shenyang's piano competition and performed his first public recital . People were shocked by his perfect performance and thought he was a real talent. From that time on, playing on the global stage became the dream of Lang Lang and his parents. To help him much closer to his dream, when Lang was 9, his father quit his job and went with Lang to Beijing to help his son study piano. There, Lang did not receive the praise that he had rece...\n\nQ: When did Lang Lang perform his first public recital?", "options": ["In 1989", "In 1987", "In 1999", "In 1990"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 540, "question": "It was 11 pm. Donald Lubeck was lying in bed. Outside, lightning lit up the sky, and thunder shook the house. Suddenly he heard the smoke alarm sounding. Lubeck walked down to see what happened; he opened the door to the kitchen, and flames just went out. The sudden strong wind from the doorway immediately created a large fire from a small one, probably caused by lightning. Lubeck went back to his bedroom to call 911. \"I felt safe because the room had a separate stairway,\" he explains. The phone didn't work, and when Lubeck tried to go down the stairway, he was stopped by a wall of flames. Lubeck realized he was in trouble. His daughter and granddaughters, who lived with him, were away for the night. Up a hill lived Lubeck's neighbors, Jeremie Wentworth and his wife. From his house, Wentwo...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that Donald Lubeck  _  .", "options": ["was living alone", "trusts Jeremie Wentworth", "got in touch with 911", "sounded the smoke alarm himself"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 750, "question": "We do not know when man first began to use salt, but we do know that it has been used in many different ways throughout history. Historical evidence shows, for example, that people who lived over 3,000 years ago ate salted fish. Thousands of years ago in Egypt, salt was used to preserve the dead. Stealing salt was considered a major crime during some periods of history. In the eighteenth century, for example, if a person was caught stealing salt, he could be put in prison and his ears could be cut off. In the Roman Empire, one of the most important roads was the one that carried salt from the salt mines to Rome. Guards were stationed along the route to protect against salt thieves, and they received their pay in salt, thus bringing the English word, salary. Any guard who fell asleep while ...\n\nQ: The main purpose of the text is to tell readers   _  .", "options": ["how salt was found and got", "salt is important in people's life", "salt was difficult to get in the past", "what salt brings to the English language"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2267, "question": "People appear to be born to calculate. The numerical skills of children develop so early that it is easy to imagine an internal clock of mathematical maturity guiding their growth. Not long after learning to walk and talk, they can set the table with impressive accuracy--one plate, one knife, one spoon, one fork for each of the five chairs. Soon they are capable of noting that they have placed five knives, spoons and forks on the table, and a bit later, that this amounts to fifteen pieces of silverware. Having thus mastered addition, some people expect that if a child were on a desert island at birth and brought back seven years later, he or she could enter a second-grade mathematics class without any serious problems of intellectual adjustment. Of course, the truth is not so simple. This ...\n\nQ: In this passage the author's attitude towards \"children numerical skills\" is   _  .", "options": ["critical", "approving", "questioning", "objective"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3041, "question": "Welcome to Gold Coast Wax Museum HIGHLIGHTS The Gold Wax Museum is one of the Cold Coast's longest running attractions. It's a collection of famous figures. It's Australia's largest museum of its kind, featuring more than 110 life-size wax figures copies of British and Australian History. The Wax Museum is visited by many thousands of people each year who are shocked at the amazing realism of the life-size figures in authentic costumes. This is your invitation to wander through at your leisure and meet many important and famous people's figures on Queensland's Gold Coast. Come face to face with such celebrities as Michael Jackson, President Obama, past President John F. Kennedy, King Hussein, members of the Royal Family, and many others whose lives have all left an indelible mark on our wo...\n\nQ: If a couple and their l0-year-old son visit the Gold Coast Wax Museum, they may pay  _  .", "options": ["$87", "$80", "$68", "$58"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1257, "question": "Yang Qunhui, 28, a graduate of Chengdu University of Information Technology, Sichuan Province, gave up her job with a monthly salary of 20,000 yuan ($3,014) at a famous company, but has started her own restroom-ad business with five other graduates, becoming a \"restroom queen.\" The company, opened in May, is now the only one of its kind in Chengdu. It has two goals: to find suitable restrooms to place ads and to find clients who are willing to put their ads in them. \"We are now trying to find restrooms to place the ads. A larger area means more ad sources,\" said Yang. Yang got the idea to run the company one year ago when she looked for toilet repairing information on the Internet but finally noticed companies in Beijing and Shanghai doing restroom ads. \"It's so interesting,\" she said. \"Ev...\n\nQ: This passage mainly tells us that   _  .", "options": ["a young woman called Yang Qunhui has started her restroom-ad business.", "restroom ads have advantages including low price and easy words.", "many people think restroom ads are effective because they can kill the time.", "people tend to remember lots of things while sitting or standing in the loo."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 672, "question": "Two new studies have investigated why fewer women, compared to men, study and work in the so-called STEM subjects in the United States: science, technology, engineering and mathematics. The American Association of University Women(AAUW) examined existing research. Its report \"Why So Few?\" suggested ways to interest more girls and women in the STEM fields. The researchers found that cultural and environmental factors make a difference. Researcher Christianne Corbett says more boys than girls score very high on math tests in most countries, but Iceland and Thailand are exceptions. \"This is something that we point out in our report--that cultural factors and societal factors can make a difference in who achieves at the very high levels and whether girls are achieving or not.\" Another study ca...\n\nQ: Which of the following are mentioned as important factors for women to go into the STEM fields according to the passage?", "options": ["Gender and age.", "Culture and environment.", "Study and work experience.", "Family background."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1576, "question": "\"Humans have a code of ethics ,\" says Marc Bekoff, an animal behavior expert at the University of Colorado. \" If I don't play in a certain way, you won't play with me. Some animals have the same code.\" Scientists recently discovered that animals that live in groups, such as elephants, foxes, and wolves, are especially likely to follow rules. If they don't, and each does its own thing, the group might break apart. Group members would be forced to live alone. Then they'd have a harder time hunting and raising their young. That's probably why a traveling wolf pack stopped and waited to let its slowly moving leader catch up. Similar social ties may have caused a captive elephant to save her friend from drowning. Selfish reasons certainly motivated the male fox, who wanted to keep playing. Some...\n\nQ: It can be learned from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["following rules makes it easy for animals to seek for mates", "some animals like to follow the examples of human beings", "some animals also have a code of ethics like human beings", "following rules is common behavior of all animals"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3133, "question": "I still remember my first day at school in London and I was half-excited and half-frightened. On my way to school I wondered what sort of questions the other boys would ask me and practiced all the answers: \"I am nine years old. I was born here but I haven't lived here since I was two. I was living in Farley. It's about thirty miles away. I came back to London two months ago.\" I also wondered if it was the custom for boys to fight strangers like me, but I was tall for my age. I hoped they would decide not to risk it. No one took any notice of me before school. I stood in the center of the playground, expecting someone to say \"hello\", but no one spoke to me. When a teacher called my name and told me where my classroom was, one or two boys looked at me but that was all. My teacher was called...\n\nQ: The writer was offered a handkerchief because  _  .", "options": ["he threw himself down and saved the goal", "he pushed a player on the other team", "he was beginning to be accepted", "he was no longer a newcomer"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3146, "question": "Working Wives Last week, we published an article about modern marriage. A recent survey showed that in England 51 percent of married women go out to work . people were asked what they thought of \"working wives\". The results were as follow: Men Women In favor 70% 80% Against 10% 20% Don't know 20% 0% We asked readers to write and tell us their opinions. Here are some of the hundreds of letters we received. I'm a (woman)photographer. I make plenty of money, travel a lot, and meet a lot of people. I enjoy my work, and would hate to stay at home. I would never marry a man who wanted me to give up my work. Ms. Jojo O Leary Hampstead At present there are over 1,000,000 unemployed men in Britain. If a woman gets a job, she puts one more man out of work. Perhaps that man has a wife and twelve chil...\n\nQ: Last week we published an article about   _  .", "options": ["marriage nowadays", "working women", "working wives", "a strange marriage"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1922, "question": "Ad.1 West High School Bake Sale Come and support our band and buy some delicious baked goods! Friday, September 20th, 2:00 - 4:00 p.m. In the hall by the office after school Cookies: 25 cents each or 5 for $1 Brownies: 50 cents each or 3 for $1.25 Cake by the slice: $1 Whole cakes: $8 Proceeds go toward sending our band to Nationals. Ad.2 SHIPPING AND HANDLING CHARGES Ups or U.S. Parcel Post are the standard methods for continental U.S. shipments. ORDER TOTAL GROUND EXPEDITED GROUND 9-12 working days 4-5 working days $0.00 to $30.00 $4.50 $5.50 $30.01 to $60.00 $7.25 $8.25 $60.01 to $100.00 $9.50 $10.50 $100.01 to $200.00 $11.50 $12.50 Add $7.00 to Ground Rates for 3 Days....\n\nQ: How much money can you save   if you buy 3 brownies?", "options": ["50 cents.", "1.25 dollars.", "75 cents.", "25 cents."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 566, "question": "Opportunity knocked on my door last January when I was given a chance to work in another country. At first, it seemed really scary for me to live on my own. But I had to overcome the true challenge! Luckily, I met seven new friends, six boys and one girl. They were really nice and I loved their company. We hung out most weekends. We cooked, watched movies, chatted and shared jokes! It was amazing -- until something unexpected happened ! One of my friends was diagnosed with kidney stones which needed to be removed as soon as possible. But our friend could not afford the surgery. He tried to get help from our other friends but they refused him. My heart cried for him! Our friends abandoned him just when he needed them most. I didn't know how to help him because I didn't have any money either...\n\nQ: Why did the author go to the hospital with his friend?", "options": ["To find free medical treatment for his friend.", "To have his friend admitted into the hospital.", "To pay the expenses of treatment for his friend.", "To keep him company during the operation."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2372, "question": "Take That Tiger Mom In the ongoing battle between Tiger Moms, French Mamas, and everyone else who wants to know what is the best way to raise their kids, a new study adds evidence that the extreme Tiger-style may do more harm than good. Authoritarian parents are more likely to end up with disrespectful children with violent behaviors, the study found, compared to parents who listen to their kids with the goal of gaining trust. It was the first study to look at how parenting styles affect the way teens view their parents and, in turn, how they behave. The study considered three general styles of parenting. Authoritative parents are demanding and controlling while also being warm and sensitive to their children's needs. Authoritarian parents, on the contrary, are demanding and controlling wi...\n\nQ: Tiger Moms and French Mamas are mentioned in the passage to   _  .", "options": ["give an example of authoritarian parenting", "show the advantage of parenting", "compare two types of parenting", "introduce the topic"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2626, "question": "Men sometimes say: \"We are better and cleverer than women. Women never invented things. We do.\" It is true that men have invented a lot of useful things: the alphabet, machines, rockets, and guns, too. But scientists and archeologists now agree that women invented one very important thing. It had changed the history. They invented agriculture. Before the invention of agriculture men were hunter. They went out every day. Sometimes they killed animals-sometimes animals killed them. Life was difficult and dangerous. Women had to go out every day, too. They collected roots, fruit and grass. Then, one day, more than 10,000years ago a woman dropped some grass seeds. She dropped them near her home in the Middle East. They grew--and the first wheat was born. The idea grew, too. Women planted roots...\n\nQ: Sometimes men think that   _  .", "options": ["they have rights as equal as women", "women have changed the history", "they have more abilities than history", "women are not so bright as they are"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 685, "question": "Dear John, My name is Amber and I want to share my story with you because what you've shared about life and positive energy has changed my life. This past year has been one of the hardest for me. I felt I was stuck in a position that had nothing to do with what I wanted to do with my life. In January, after two years of being together, my boyfriend left me. I read your blog every morning as I drink my coffee at work, but it wasn't until this March that I told myself \"no more negativity\" as you taught readers in your blog. Since then I've got into new habits at work to keep my energy positive. When people walk in the front door, I'm the first face they see, so I smile big when I say \"good morning\" to them, especially on Mondays. Instead of waiting for someone to ask me for help, I offer it ...\n\nQ: Amber wrote the letter mainly to  _", "options": ["introduce herself to John", "talk about her bad year", "ask for some advice", "express her thanks"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 826, "question": "There are millions of used cell phones in the world today. Most of them just lay in our houses without any purpose. Every day dozens of new cell phone models appear. Today, you can find what was regarded as a fantasy yesterday in store and you will buy it tomorrow. But what to do with the old phones, which work well enough and not so old? Just get some money! Simply Sellular is buying almost all models of cell phones: LG, Motorola, Siemens, Samsung, Sanyo, Nokia and many other cell phones. Also they accept phones produced in every country, and in every condition. Simply Sellular can offer a good price for your old cell phone in cash. Their mission is giving you a simple way to get money for an old phone, as simple and profitable, as possible. Also they offer a trade-in scheme to get anothe...\n\nQ: This passage is written mainly to   _  .", "options": ["warn people of the risks of using cell phones", "introduce to us what to do with our old cell phones", "advise people not to change cell phones frequently", "encourage us to keep up with new technology"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2343, "question": "Have you ever intended to be fully absorbed in your work but found yourself distracted by e-mail, the Internet and other things throughout the day? According to the survey made by a famous university in the USA, most people have the experience. \"People often lose their concentration when they are bored, of course, but also when they are engaged in challenging tasks,\" says Peter Bregman, the head of the survey. \"They sometimes have a feeling to escape from what's difficult or boring, so they jump out,\" he says. The part of the brain devoted to attention is connected to the brain's emotional center. Any strong emotion --quarrels with colleagues, problems at home --can interrupt our attention. Studies over the last decade have shown that too much work to do at a time can easily lead to distra...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which is NOT the reason why some people can be distracted from their work?", "options": ["They don't want to be devoted to their work.", "They are disturbed by the Internet and other things.", "They can't find interest in their work.", "They feel their work is too hard for them."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3302, "question": "Street art can be found on buildings, sidewalks, street signs and even trash cans from Tokyo to Paris to New York City. This special kind of art can take the form of paintings, sculptures, cloth or even stickers. Street art has become part of a global visual culture. Now, even art museums and galleries are collecting the work of street artists. It is not easy to provide an exact history of the street art movement. This kind of art has developed in many kinds of ways in places all over the world. Also, because it is illegal to paint public and private property without permission, street artists usually work secretly. This secretive nature of street art and its countless forms make it hard to define exactly. And people have different opinions about the movement. Some think street art is a cr...\n\nQ: The city officials used to do away with graffiti probably because  _  .", "options": ["they caused arguments between people", "they were ugly in someone's eyes", "they were not painted under proper guidance", "they didn't express good traditional culture."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 442, "question": "You could feel sorry for Alberto Torres, who is blind. The last thing he remembers seeing was his daughter being born 13 years ago. Then the world went blank; he can only imagine what his only child looks like now, as a teenaged honor student. Bad luck is no stranger to this warm and thoughtful 37-year-old man. His mother died of cancer when he was 4, and his father, who was often ill, had to give him up to the care of the state when he was 11. He later worked for 19 years in a workshop making household goods, deathly boring work. Earlier this month, Alberto Torres's wife, who had just been laid off from her job, had to have a breast removed due to cancer and now faces a year of radiation treatments. Things seemed always to go from almost incredibly bad to worse. Even Mr. Torres's good luc...\n\nQ: Mr. Torres works very hard in order to   _  .", "options": ["make plenty of money", "win his supervisor's trust", "live like a normal person", "complete his daily task"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2520, "question": "A young man went to a town and worked there. He did not have a wife and a servant did the work in his house. The young man liked laughing a lot. He nailed the servant's shoes to the floor on Monday, and then laughed, because he put his feet in them and fell down. The servant was not angry, but smiled. Then the young man put brushes in his bed on Tuesday. The servant got into bed and hit the brushes with his feet. He was afraid. The young man laughed loudly again. Again the servant was not angry, but smiled. Then on Wednesday the young man said to his servant, \"You're a nice, kind man. I am not going to be unkind to you again.\" The servant smiled and said, \"And I'm not going to put any more mud from the street in your coffee.\"...\n\nQ: What did the servant do in return to the young man?", "options": ["He stole something from the house.", "He gave a smile to the young man.", "He had a fight with him.", "He put mud into the young man's coffee."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1686, "question": "Americans often say that there are only two things a person can be sure of:death and taxes.Many people feel that the United States has the worst taxes in the world. Taxes are the money that people pay to support their government.There are generally three levels of government in the United States:federal,state,and city;therefore,there are three types of taxes. Salaried people who can earn more than four to five thousand dollars per year must pay a certain part.It depends on their salaries.The federal government has a two-level income tax:that is,15 or 28 percent.$17 850 is the cut off.The tax rate is 15 percent below $17 850 and 28 percent above. The second tax is for the state government:New York,California,or any of the other forty-eight states.Some states have an income tax similar to th...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Different levels of the governments have different types of taxes in the United States.", "All the states have a sales tax which is used to support poor people.", "The tax of the states is similar to that of the federal government.", "All the states use both taxes to raise their income every year to build schools."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3004, "question": "People bury treasure to stop other people from taking it. They choose a quiet place, dig a deep hole and bury the treasure in it. Then they make a map of where the treasure is or write down other clues that will help them or someone else to find it again. In Britain a few years ago, a writer wrote about some treasure that he had buried. He put clues in the story to help readers find it. Thousands of people hunted for the treasure. They dug holes all over Britain, hoping to find it. One of the most popular adventure stories ever written is Robert Louis Stephenson's \"Treasured Island\", an exciting story about a young boy, Jim Hawkins, who is captured by pirates and later finds some buried treasure. Then there is the true story about a man who had to travel overseas for a year. He did not tru...\n\nQ: People who bury treasure usually    _    .", "options": ["do not trust banks", "have a little money .", "want to live in a quiet place.", "expect to lose it"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2967, "question": "With around 40,000 students, the Politecnico di Milano is the largest and most technical university in Italy, offering undergraduate, graduate and other courses in engineering, architecture and design. Founded in 1863, just two years after Italy was united, Milan Polytechnic is international famous. Many of its graduates now work in big companies abroad like M.I.T., Caltech and Oxbridge. Yet the Politechnic has a problem. As you know, here in Italy people speak Italian. Beautiful though the language may be, it is not a good choice for engineers when they're building a way in Norway or designing a bridge in Vietnam. For better or worse, the global tongue of engineers is English. Hoping to attract more international students, the Politechnic decided to run its doctor's courses in English onl...\n\nQ: Which statement is NOT the reason why the Politechnic decided to use only English in class?", "options": ["Many graduates work abroad.", "Italian is widely used.", "English is the global language.", "The Politechnic is an international university."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2011, "question": "Japan' s nuclear crisis is also causing concerns in China. Worried shoppers rushed to stores and supermarkets in the country for salt, with the belief that it might protect them from potential nuclear radiation spreading from Japan. Many rushed to buy to store as much iodized salt as possible because of the rumor that iodized salt could help prevent radiation poisoning spreading from Japan' s Fukushima Daiichi power plant. Consumers also worried that the nuclear plumes might spread to China by air and sea, polluting food sources, including salt taken from the sea. The wave of panic buying spread quickly across the country, driving up salt prices by five to ten fold in some cities. Even regions rich in salt production, like Jiangxi Province,faced sudden shortages. The government took measur...\n\nQ: People made panic purchases of salt for the reasons EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["salt might protect them from potential nuclear radiation", "nuclear radiation might pollute food sources", "nuclear radiation might pollute salt taken from the sea", "there would be a shortage of salt on the market"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2956, "question": "The southwest of Australia has been named as one of 25\"hot spots\" for future species extinction because of global warming.A new study says global warming will become a top cause of extinction across the world,with thousands of species of plantsand animals likely to be wiped out in the coming decades. According to the study,global warming ranks among the most serious threats to the planet's biodiversity and,under some conditions,may be more than that due to deforestation.This study provides even stronger scientific evidence that global warming will result in catastrophic species losses across the planet.Last month,a UN study said humans were responsible for the worst extinction and urged extra efforts to reach a UN target of slowing the rate of losses by 2010. Scientists disagree about how ...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Australia Named as Extinction\"Hot Spot\"", "Global Warming and Species Extinction", "Global Warming is Number One Killer", "Australia on the Edge of Extinction"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 679, "question": "We're surrounded by chemistry in everyday life. Sometimes it is easy to see, like when your science teacher does a big experiment in class. At other times, it can be pretty hard to see everyday chemistry at work, but nearly everything you touch or use has some element of chemistry in it. Something as simple as toothpaste contains at least three chemicals, if not more. It is the mixture of them and its chemical reaction that keeps your teeth clean. Other things you use every day are created by chemistry, such as hair products, shampoo and soap. Adding detergent to water involves chemistry. Without chemistry, we would never have known that we need soap to get the oil out of clothes or skin. Chemistry not only helps us make products for use, but it also helps us understand the world around us...\n\nQ: The following actions are about chemistry EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["cleaning teeth with toothpaste", "washing hair with hair products", "using soap to get the oil out of clothes", "washing your face with water"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3160, "question": "TheCastle of Monteriggioni Located in central Tuscany,the Castle of Monteriggioniwas built by the Republic of Siena at the beginning of the 13th century in orderto defend its southern border against Florence.With their impressive towers, they feature in Dante's Divine Comedy. MainSights Inside the town are the Church of Santa Maria Assunta,the battlements on the town walls and the small \"Monteriggioni in Arme\" museum, where there are models andlife-size armors . Every July within the wall of the town a special eventis celebrated: the Medieval Festival of Monteriggioni, one of the mostbeautiful festivals in the region. The city goes back in time to the MiddleAges, the streets are filled up with people in period costume creating a realatmosphere. Dances, live performances, music, theatre, ki...\n\nQ: Where can this article be probably found?", "options": ["In a travel guidebook.", "In a textbook.", "In a fashion magazine.", "In a newspaper."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1539, "question": "When I left my bag on a train, I lost my most precious possession, a small framed photograph of my great grandparents, Emily and Gordon Baker. The frame was made of silver, with an elegant flower design in one corner. The photograph was taken in March 1939 on their wedding day. Emily looked very happy, and Gordon looked rather alarmed. A few months later, he was killed in action in North Africa. I received the photograph when my aunt Mabel died. I'm a student at Edinburgh University and I live in an old Edwardian house. At the end of last term, I packed a large bag and a small bag and set off for London, where I was planning to catch the Eurostar train to Paris. Minutes after getting off the train at Kings Cross Station, I realized that I'd left the small bag in the overhead luggage rack. ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred that the author felt  _  when he found the silver photo on Bay.", "options": ["nervous", "excited", "disappointed", "worried"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 752, "question": "Do you like chocolate? Maybe most people do. A box of it can be a great gift. Buy one for a friend and give it as a surprise. See how happy that person gets. Say you just got a box of chocolate. Which piece do you pick first? A man has studied people's choices. He says they tell something about the person. Did you choose a round piece? You are a person who likes to party. Did you choose an oval shape? You are a person who likes to make things. Picking a square shape shows something else. The person is honest and truthful. You can depend on him or her. What kind of chocolate do you pick? Maybe you like milk chocolate. This shows you have warm feelings about the past. Dark chocolate means something else. A person who chooses it looks toward the future. What about white chocolate? Would you c...\n\nQ: This passage mainly tells us   _  .", "options": ["why people like chocolate", "almost everyone likes chocolate", "about different kinds of chocolate", "different choices may show different characters"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1976, "question": "We found out that Jenny was suffering hearing loss when she was four and a half years old. Several operations and speech classes later, when she was seven, we found out that Jenny had Juvenile Rheumatoid Arthritis . She could not put pressure on the heels of her feet, so she walked on tiptoe , and when the pain became unbearable, I carried her. Jenny was fortunate, though, because she did not suffer the deformities , often associated with JRA. All through grade school, and on into high school, Jenny suffered, yet never complained. She took her medicine, and I would often wrap her feet in steaming towels, and hold her until the pain eased. But, as soon as she could stand the pain, Jenny, immediately, carried on, as though she were pain-free. She wore a smile on her face, a song on her lips,...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that Jenny  _  .", "options": ["was very sensitive to what others thought of her", "was active but pessimistic about her misfortune", "attached great importance to group honor", "was positive about her life and achieved a lot"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3439, "question": "In the world today, there are millions of surveillance cameras, or \"spy cams\", watching and monitoring our daily activities. There are some benefits of course, as people who are breaking laws can be watched and caught using cameras and this helps keep our society and public places safe. These cameras are everywhere and most are openly visible on roads, in airports, businesses, shopping centers and government buildings and even in lifts. Even schools have started using spy cams to watch student activity and behaviour. The cameras are so common now that we hardly ever even notice them. But the problem lies with the ones that are hidden away from our eyes and are unseen. Technology has helped develop tiny cameras that can be very well hidden and they can \"spy\" on shoppers, workers, babysitter...\n\nQ: Spy cams will be more widely used in the future because   _  .         .", "options": ["all people want to spy", "of the invasion of privacy", "people enjoy being watched", "of terrorist attacks"], "answer": 3}]